teenpinkcollection.com 2010-01-02

# TeenPinkVideos.com Spam Policy

PRIVACY POLICY FOR  
WWW.TEENPINKVIDEOS.COM  
Effective Date: May 16, 2006  
Last Updated: May 16, 2006 

I. General.

A. The operative parties referred to in this policy are COMPANY and you, the user of this site.

1\. TPV, LLC, is the publisher and operator of various websites and is hereinafter referred to as "COMPANY". When first-person pronouns are used in this Policy, (us, we, our, ours, etc.) these provisions are referring to TPV, LLC, d/b/a www.teenpinkvideos.com. Additionally, when the terms "The SITE" or "SITE" are used, these terms refer to www.teenpinkvideos.com.

2\. You, the User – As the user of this SITE, this policy will refer to the user as "you" or through any second-person pronouns, such as "yours," etc. Hereinafter, the user of the SITE shall be referred to in applicable second-person pronouns.

B. This Privacy Policy describes how we use information received about you when you visit our SITE or when you subscribe to, or otherwise use our online services. This Policy does not cover any information that we may receive from or about you through channels other than through the use of the SITE. 

II. Revisions To This Policy.

We reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. You should periodically check for any modifications of this Policy by re-visiting this web page and using the "refresh" button on your browser. You should note the date of last revision to this Policy, which appears at the top of this Policy. If the "last modified" date remains unchanged after you have clicked the "refresh" button on your browser, you may presume that no changes have been made since the last reading of the policy. A changed "last modified" dates indicates that this Policy has been updated or edited, and the updated or edited version supersedes any prior versions immediately upon posting.

III. Personal Information That We Collect.

Visitors to our SITE and services will have multiple manners of interactivity with us. Depending upon your level of interaction, we will collect different information about you. The type of information collected is as follows:

A. Members - Members are those users who subscribe to our services. Members will be prompted to provide their name, their address, their age, their telephone number, e-mail address, and any other necessary billing information. Credit card information is collected by a SITE's third-party billing processor. 

B. Non-Members – Non-Members are visitors to the site who do not subscribe to our service. Non-Members never enter into any active data collection pages. Any information gathered from Non-Members is also gathered from Members but, in the case of the former, limited to cookies, IP Addresses and Referral URLs, and other passive information gathering devises (explained below). 

IV. How We Collect Information From You.

A. Passive Collection – We use cookies to collect information about you in order to enhance your experience on the site. The information collected in our cookies includes, but is not limited to, your user IP address and other session data. 

B. Active Collection – we collect information from you when you complete or attempt to complete registration forms to sign up for your membership on our Site. Locations for such collection are registration pages, such as http://secure.teenpinkvideos.com/signup/signup.php?step=signup, but we reserve the right to add additional information collection portals. 

V. How We Use Your Information.

The primary use for your information is to provide you with services you have requested and/or paid for. We also use your information to deliver customized services to you; for member support purposes; and for efforts to monitor and ensure against fraud. Non-personal and aggregate information, such as that collected passively, is used in order to customize our marketing efforts or to customize the use of our site for an aggregate group of customers. We will not use the personal information of users whose membership have expired or have been cancelled in order to market our services to such individuals in the future. Rather, all such personal information will be retained for the life of the Site in the Site's protected database.

Please note, the personal information collected will not be shared with third-parties, and is only intended for use by the COMPANY. We generally will use your information for the purposes for which you specifically provide it including, for example, to ensure payment for subscription services.   
VI. Special Cases. 

It is our policy not to use or share the personal information about Non-Members or Members in ways unrelated to those described in this Policy without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, we may disclose personal information about Non-Members or Members, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: 

1\. To satisfy any laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental, or legal requests for such information; 

2\. To disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or other user policies; 

3\. To operate our Services properly; 

4\. To protect ourselves, our Members, and the general public. We specifically reserve the right to disclose any and all information to law enforcement in the event that a crime – including, but not limited to, fraud-related offense – is committed, is suspected, or if we are compelled to do so by lawful criminal, civil, or administrative process, discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders, writs, or reasonable request of authorities or persons with the reasonable power to obtain such process. 

5\. We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. Examples of such cooperation include lawful criminal, civil, or administrative process, discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders, or writs. 

VII. Transmittals From Us.

We presently do not intend to send e-mails to our Members, other than in response to specific Member inquiries; and/or in order to provide Members with system notices and other information specifically relating to your account. In the future, this policy may be subject to change, and we could opt to initiate the sending of other correspondence including, but not limited to, Member announcements. The implementation of such changes will be reflected in the Site's privacy policy. We strongly advise our Members to periodically review the terms of this policy in order to stay apprised of any such changes. 

If you provide your information to us, use the Site, or subscribe to any of our services, you will have created a commercial relationship with us. Even though the Site does not intend to provide Members with e-mail advertising materials, your use of the Site and its services constitutes your understanding and consent that even unsolicited commercial email sent from us or our affiliates is not SPAM as that term is defined under the law. 

VIII. Public Forums and Member Directories.

A. Public Forums – At the time of the institution of this Policy, we do not offer any public forums, nor do we provide services that allow Members to post messages to the public, nor to the membership at large. Nevertheless, we reserve the right to offer this service in the future. Any information, other than password and e-mail address, posted to a Forum should immediately be considered to be public information. Public forums are accessed via e-mail address, user name, and password. 

B. Member Directories – Any information provided in a user profile, member directory, or other related service should be considered to be private information. Such information will not be made public or visible in any way. 

IX. Our Commitment To Data Security. 

We take measures, including data encryption, to protect the transmission of all sensitive end-user information. We make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems. Nevertheless, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party ‘hackers' from illegally obtaining this information. We take all reasonable measures to prevent such breaches of security, but given the resourcefulness of cyber-criminals we are unable to guarantee that our security is 100% breach-proof. You assume the risk of such breaches to the extent that they occur despite our reasonable security measures.

Further, we do not provide user information to third parties; nor will we sell, rent or provide any of your information to other entities such as advertisers, or other companies selling services similar to this COMPANY's services 

X. How To Access Or Modify Your Information. 

We offer our Members the opportunity to access or modify information provided during registration. To access or modify such information, contact our Customer Service Department at support@teenpinkvideos.com.

XI. Where To Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us at support@teenpinkvideos.com.

\- End -
